http://www.sauder.com/service/privacy-policy

Collections
Shop AllAdept StorageAnda Norr®Aspen Post®August HillBarrister Lane®Beginnings®Boone Mountain®Boulevard CaféBrooklandCamden CountyCanal Street®Cannery Bridge®Canton Lane®Carson Forge®Center City™Clifford Place®Coral Cape®CostaCottage Road®County Line®Craft Pro Series®Curiod®Dakota Pass®Eden Rue®Edge Water®Englewood® Garden Villa®Granite Trace®Gruga® ChairsHammond™Harbor View®Harper Heights™Harvest Mill®Harvey Park®Heritage Hill®HomePlusHudson Court®International LuxIron City®Linden Market®Manhattan Gate®Market Commons®Metro Pike™New GrangeNew Hyde®North Avenue®Nova Loft®Office Port®Orchard Hills®Pacific View®Palladia®PinwheelPogoRadial™Rock Glen®Sauder BathSauder BoutiqueSauder SelectShoal Creek®Station House®Steel River®Stow-AwaySummit Station®Trestle®ViaViabella®Vista Key®Willow Place®
Finish
Shop All FinishesAbbey Oak®Amber PineAntigua Chestnut®Antiqued Paint®Antiqued White®Auburn Cherry®Autumn MapleBlade Walnut™Blaze Acacia®Bourbon Oak®Brew Oak™Brook CherryBrushed MapleCarbon Oak®Carolina Oak®Chalked Chestnut®Champagne Oak™Char Pine®Charcoal Ash™Charter Oak™Checked Oak®Cinnamon CherryClassic Cherry®Coastal Oak™CobblestoneCoffee Oak®Craftsman Oak®Curado Cherry®Dakota Oak®Dark Alder®Deco Stone™Diamond AshDover Oak®Ebony AshEmery Oak™EspressoEstate Black®Etched Oak™Euro OakFaux ConcreteFine Walnut™Fossil Oak®Grand Walnut®Grey AshHighland OakIron OakJamocha Wood®Laurel Oak™Lintel Oak®Milled Cherry®Milled Mesquite™Misted Elm™Mystic Oak®Northern Oak®Oiled Oak®Orchard Oak™Pacific Maple™Pale Oak®Pearl Oak™Planked Cherry®Prime Oak™Reclaimed Pine™Rich Walnut™Rum Walnut®Rustic Cedar™Salt Oak®Satin GoldScribed Oak®Select CherrySerene Walnut™Sienna Oak®Silver Sycamore™Sindoori Mango®Sky Oak®Smoked Oak™Soft BlackSoft White®Spiced Mahogany™Split Oak®Summer Oak™Urban AshVintage Oak®Washed Walnut™Washington CherryWhiteWhite Plank®Wind Oak®
Style
Shop All Styles
Bistro
Bohemian
Coastal Cottage
Contemporary
Country
Industrial
Collections
Shop AllAdept StorageAnda Norr®Aspen Post®August HillBarrister Lane®Beginnings®Boone Mountain®Boulevard CaféBrooklandCamden CountyCanal Street®Cannery Bridge®Canton Lane®Carson Forge®Center City™Clifford Place®Coral Cape®CostaCottage Road®County Line®Craft Pro Series®Curiod®Dakota Pass®Eden Rue®Edge Water®Englewood® Garden Villa®Granite Trace®Gruga® ChairsHammond™Harbor View®Harper Heights™Harvest Mill®Harvey Park®Heritage Hill®HomePlusHudson Court®International LuxIron City®Linden Market®Manhattan Gate®Market Commons®Metro Pike™New GrangeNew Hyde®North Avenue®Nova Loft®Office Port®Orchard Hills®Pacific View®Palladia®PinwheelPogoRadial™Rock Glen®Sauder BathSauder BoutiqueSauder SelectShoal Creek®Station House®Steel River®Stow-AwaySummit Station®Trestle®ViaViabella®Vista Key®Willow Place®
Finish
Shop All FinishesAbbey Oak®Amber PineAntigua Chestnut®Antiqued Paint®Antiqued White®Auburn Cherry®Autumn MapleBlade Walnut™Blaze Acacia®Bourbon Oak®Brew Oak™Brook CherryBrushed MapleCarbon Oak®Carolina Oak®Chalked Chestnut®Champagne Oak™Char Pine®Charcoal Ash™Charter Oak™Checked Oak®Cinnamon CherryClassic Cherry®Coastal Oak™CobblestoneCoffee Oak®Craftsman Oak®Curado Cherry®Dakota Oak®Dark Alder®Deco Stone™Diamond AshDover Oak®Ebony AshEmery Oak™EspressoEstate Black®Etched Oak™Euro OakFaux ConcreteFine Walnut™Fossil Oak®Grand Walnut®Grey AshHighland OakIron OakJamocha Wood®Laurel Oak™Lintel Oak®Milled Cherry®Milled Mesquite™Misted Elm™Mystic Oak®Northern Oak®Oiled Oak®Orchard Oak™Pacific Maple™Pale Oak®Pearl Oak™Planked Cherry®Prime Oak™Reclaimed Pine™Rich Walnut™Rum Walnut®Rustic Cedar™Salt Oak®Satin GoldScribed Oak®Select CherrySerene Walnut™Sienna Oak®Silver Sycamore™Sindoori Mango®Sky Oak®Smoked Oak™Soft BlackSoft White®Spiced Mahogany™Split Oak®Summer Oak™Urban AshVintage Oak®Washed Walnut™Washington CherryWhiteWhite Plank®Wind Oak®
Style
Shop All Styles
Bistro
Bohemian
Coastal Cottage
Contemporary
Country
Industrial
on all orders!
Mon-Fri 9 a.m. to 5:30 p.m. ET (closed 12-1 p.m.)
Wow, are we ever popular! Please hang in there as we meet each and every phone call, email and chat with excellence!
Privacy Policy
Information Collection and Use
Sauder Woodworking Co. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this
information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Sauder Woodworking collects information
from our users at several different points on our website.
Catalog Orders
We request information from the user on our catalog/brochure order forms. Here a user must provide contact information
(like name and shipping address). This information is used to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an
order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.
Product Registration and Other Opt-Out Sections
Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our
site at the point where we ask for the information. Our product registration form has an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who
register their product with us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address, postal address, and
telephone number off of any third party lists.
To read the complete privacy policy for our online registration, view the latest version of our registration form page.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or
contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information.
Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information
(such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information
will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user and their usage of our web
site. Our Web site uses cookies so we can "remember" information about preferences which allows users to move within our Web
site without reestablishing these settings, enhancing the user experience. Cookies can also enable us to track and target
the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. In order to perform internal market research analysis,
we may compile demographic statistics about our users based on activities such as item/dealer searches and visited pages.
Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information. If a user rejects the cookie, they may
still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site and user
preferences will not be stored for future browsing. For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our
Sweepstakes, Contests or monthly Drawings that occasionally take place.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic
information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Sharing
We collect aggregated demographic information on our site. For instance, on our dealer locator searches we track the search
details (including zip code, product model number and date searched). This is not linked to any personal information that
can identify any individual person. This information may be shared with our business partners.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we [Sauder Woodworking Co.] are not responsible for the
privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy
statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies
solely to information collected by this web site.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our policy page so our users are always aware of
what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
Please enter a valid email address.
Email Preferences
© 2020 - Sauder Woodworking Co. All rights reserved.
Please enter a valid email address.
Email Preferences
© 2020 - Sauder Woodworking Co. All rights reserved.
Privacy Policy   Accessibility
X
Email Subscription
Check your inbox for an activation email confirming your subscription.
You currently have a subscription.
There has been an issue.
